[theme music]
Guess what happened last week.
I don't have to guess
'cause we're gonna show
everybody the highlights.
Oh, good, because
I can't remember everything.
If I had a song
like "Forever"
I'll bet Fat Fish Records
would sign us...like that.
You want it, you got it.
I'd no choice,
I had to sign him.
- Honey, he signed you.
- Congratulations.
- I don't dance.
- Don't worry about it.
'Cause when we get
through with you..
...everyone in this country
will be dancing, "The Jess Man".
"The Jess Man?"
What's gonna happen next,
Michelle?
I can't tell you.
- Why? Is it a secret?
- No, because I just don't know.
[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman
the paperboy evening TV ♪
♪ When did I get to living here
Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This whole worlds
confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean
as you'll ever see ♪
♪ Ain't a bird
who knows your tune ♪
♪ Then a little voice
inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell your dreams
so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold onto ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there
and you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Oh, Steph,
you can't hang out in here.
Uncle Jesse's gonna get
his first dance lesson.
I know, I got a front row seat.
[doorbell ringing]
Oh, Jess, the guys
from Fat Fish Music are here.
(Jess)
'I'll get it.'
You know, Uncle Jesse's been
working on his dancing
for a couple of days,
he's come a long way.
I'm dancing.
Hey, you're right.
He's really improved.
- Jess, babe. Come here.
- Dave, babe. Hit me.
I'd like you to meet one of the
hottest video directors
and choreographers
in the biz, Richard Williams.
Hey, hi, Richard.
How you doing?
- Whoa!
- See?
He's good. He's very good.
Hey, listen, about this
whole dance thing now..
Guys, let's rethink this.
"Forever" is not really a dance
song, it's more of a ballad.
Not anymore.
We've re-recorded it
and now it's a rap song.
Listen, David,
I'm not, not really a rapper.
Vanilla Ice said the same thing.
Look, I've got a hot new concept
for your video.
Well, it's gonna be like a whole
Arabian Genie thing.
You're gonna love it.
It's the perfect way to get all
of America doing "The Jess Man."
Again with "The Jess Man."
I'm not really a dancer.
Hey, Jess Man,
dancing is just a matter
of putting a lot of little
isolated movements together.
- Simple.
- Alright, I'll try it.
- You show me what to do.
- Sure, start like this.
- Okay. Got that.
- Yeah, good.
Now, add your shoulders
like this.
- Don't stop moving your head.
- Oh, right. Yeah, just..
Got it. Got it.
Now, add your hips like this.
Oh, but don't stop moving
your head and shoulders.
- Yeah, the whole..
- Yeah.
Right, see, I got..
I'm dancing everybody, I got it.
No problem. I can dance.
Yeah, hold up, hold up, hold up.
Maybe we should start with
something just a little simpler.
Umm, The Running Man.
Something like this.
Now, open your legs
from side to side, man.
I do kind
of a Sammy Running Man.
I should get goin',
should get goin'.
It's easy, Uncle Jesse.
Come on, Aunt Becky, ready.
(Richard)
'Yeah.'
Well, at least someone
in the family can dance.
I can sing too.
♪ I believe the children
are our future ♪
Thank you, Stephanie.
♪ Teach them well ♪
♪ And let them lead the way ♪♪
Thank you, Stephanie.
That's enough, thanks.
This is not a telethon.
See, I'm not,
I can't dance.
I really don't
know how to dance.
But you will.
Jess Man,
for the next 48 hours
you are going
to move your body
in ways you never
thought possible.
Will this involve pain?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, good.
But check it out,
you'll end up looking like this.
Hit me.
[upbeat music]
Oh, I got..
I can do that.
Come on, you can do it.
Let the music move you.
Right.
Yeah, come on,
give it a little bit more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, give me that kick.
- Give me that kick.
- I got the kick. Whoa.
Yeah, yeah.
Now go for that finish.
Here it goes, and a..
Becky, ice.
Okay, now, let's make a toast
to your first day
in the lemonade business.
One for you and one for me.
Cheers.
- More sugar.
Better put another teaspoon in.
Well, that ought to wake you up
and rot your teeth.
Michelle, it won't be long
before you earn enough money
to buy youself that ant farm.
I hope so.
Because my little friends can't
live on this lollipop forever.
- You had a great lesson, Deej.
- Thanks, Kimmy.
I think my dad was pretty
impressed with my driving.
Thank God, I'm alive.
You know, T-man, for an uptight
guy, you stayed pretty cool.
Yeah, Kimmy, no sweat.
Get your lemonade.
It's good idea.
I could use a cup.
You could use
some dress shields.
Kimmy, you could use
some exercise.
Take a hike.
That would be 10 cents, mister.
Alright. Thank you, sweetheart.
Mmm.
Couple more sips of this
and I'll need dentures.
You know what, honey,
I don't have any change
all I have is a dollar.
That's no problem. Thank you.
Michelle, I just
gave you a dollar.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Oh, yeah. Have a nice day.
Danny, always read the front
and the back.
Joey, that's your handwriting.
You owe me 90 cents.
Pay up.
Deej, bad news.
I can't study in Spain
this summer
unless I pass my spanish class.
Will you help me?
Yeah, I don't wanna spend six
weeks in Spain without you.
Why do I have to learn
the whole language?
All I need to know
are three words.
Food, boys and bathroom.
True, but you don't
wanna get them mixed up.
[speaking spanish]
No time for dancing,
we have to go study.
[instrumental music]
"Forever" video, take 27.
And action.
[instrumental music]
[upbeat music]
♪ If every single word I said
is gonna make you laugh ♪
♪ If every song I sing to you
will fill your heart with joy ♪
♪ Yo I'm gonna hang ♪
♪ How long ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ I ask the skies what we had
if we had why do I have ♪
♪ The love I have for you ♪
♪ Is going to live
inside your heart ♪
♪ It's gonna hang ♪
♪ How long ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Did it just now ♪
Cut. Take a break.
Well, I think it's going very
well, don't you?
We've been here
for six hours
and I don't have one frame
of usable film.
Yeah, but, this..
This tuna? Great.
Jess Man. Jess Man.
Jess man, do you have control
of any of your body parts?
Well, I do, I do. I just..
Theoretically,
really it's not my fault.
My whole leg fell asleep
while I was crouching
in that silly hamper.
Well, that's true.
He has very bad circulation.
Becky, you don't need
to make excuses for me.
I do have this circulation thing
that happens--
- Jess Man..
- Guys, come on, I told you.
- I can't dance.
- I'm surprised you can walk.
This is not the "Forever"
that I wanna do.
This is not my kind of music.
These are not my pants.
Jesse, trust us.
We know what we're doing.
But, I can't believe I went
through with this silly thing.
Come on, Becky, we're out
of here. I quit, pal.
Wait a minute. Here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Are you crazy?
This is your one shot
at makin' it.
You can't just walk out, babe.
Watch me, babe.
[instrumental music]
Oh, my God, what have I done?
I gotta go crawling back
to Fat Fish Music.
Maybe if I beg 'em,
they'll give me a second chance.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys,
I was so selfish.
I wasn't even thinking
of you two.
I mean, I could have you
totally set up.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, with college,
trust funds..
...toupees if the hair thing
never happens for you.
Well, I promise, guys,
I won't let you down.
I love you so much.
Give me a chew.
[instrumental music]
Okay, Kimmy, conjugate
the verb jugar to play.
Please, Deej, I can't conjugate
any more Spanish.
It's after midnight.
Can't we go to sleep?
En Espanol.
El sleep-o beg-o please-o.
[knocking on door]
(Danny)
'Deej, you sleeping
with your light on again?'
Uh, one sec, dad,
I'm just getting into bed.
You were supposed to go home
two hours ago, hide.
Kimmy, get out of there.
Deej, is everything okay?
Sweetie, you been up studying
all this time?
Si.
- Deej, you must be exhausted.
- Si.
You know what,
let me give you a kiss.
No.
So, Deej,
you must be real excited
about your trip
to Spain this summer.
Si.
I hope you take my advice
about ditching Kimmy.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, it's all set up.
Pepe, the pinata maker..
...he's gonna wrap her
in papier mache
and then hang her
in the village square.
And all the little
village children
are gonna come in
with their flaming sticks.
Flaming sticks?
I got you, gibbler.
You can come out, Deej.
Sorry, dad.
I'm trying to help Kimmy
with her Spanish.
Kimmy, go home.
If you wanna pass that test,
you'll need your sleep, okay?
- Buenas noches.
- Oh, nachos, great.
I'm starving.
Maybe a couple more minutes
of studying wouldn't hurt.
[instrumental music]
Okay, Michelle, $8 and 40 cents.
You sell one more cup of
lemonade
and you'll have enough money
to buy yourself that ant farm.
Joey, please, buy one more cup.
Michelle,
I've already had 50 cups.
I'm sweating lemon juice.
You don't need to drink it,
just buy it.
Why didn't I think of that
49 cups ago?
You're absolutely right.
Okay, here you go.
Jess, come on,
are you sure you wanna do this
"I Dream of Jesse" video?
I'd rather do the video my way,
but I think of you
and our children
and our future.
It's too bad you can't just
buy your own record company.
Yeah.
I'm just a few bucks short, huh?
You could have
my ant farm money.
Sweetheart, that's
the greatest offer I ever got.
But you worked hard
for that money.
You keep that money, okay?
But I love you and you're
important than my ants.
Sorry, guys.
[doorbell rings]
Yeah, that's Janolari.
I wish there was another way
out of this.
David.
Uh, I'm sorry I blew up and I'd
like you to accept my apology.
Mmm-hm, I knew
you'd come crawling back.
Let's face it, without
Fat Fish Music, you're nothin'.
Who else would make you
an offer like we did?
Yeah, it's funny that you
mentioned that
because you know
just before you got here
I received a very-very
interesting new offer.
What offer? From who?
Well..
...it's a 5 year old company.
Small but very generous
and they really love me.
Yeah? What kind of money
are they talking about?
Big money.
Enough to buy a farm.
You know what, Dave, you're
starting to remind me of the guy
who turned down the Beatles.
- What guy?
- It doesn't matter.
He's the laughing stock
of the music business.
Never heard from again, yup.
He's still kicking himself
about that one.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure you'll get another job.
Can you say, "Would you
like fries with that, sir?"
Jess, are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious. Listen.
David, I.. I gotta go..
I gotta go with a company
that believes in me.
Hey, we believe, we believe.
Hey, look, I know we had
our creative differences
but that's the way
the biz is.
You work, you fight,
you do lunch, you compromise.
We'll do the song my way
or there's no deal.
You got it. See?
Now we're compromising.
- Jess, babe.
- Hey, babe. Hit me. Come on.
Okay.
- Love you.
- Right back at you.
What a goon.
- We did it.
- Way to go, Jess.
- Alright, honey.
- Thank you, guys. Alright.
Oh, Michelle, I couldn't
have done it without you.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what I did
but I'm glad I did it.
A hundred kisses.
One, two, three, four, five..
[instrumental music]
Hola, Tanneritos.
I gotta change the locks again.
Hey, Kimmy, did you get your
grades?
They just came in the mail.
I passed Spanish.
- Isn't that muy awesome?
- Kimmy, we're going to Spain.
Let me see that, Kimmy.
Whoa! You got a D minus.
Well, your parents
must be very proud.
Yeah, my dad says
with grades like this
I'm on the fast track
to air-conditioning school.
Hey, everybody, come on.
I'm gonna be on MTV in a minute.
Joey, girls, come in here.
I'm gonna be on MTV.
Comet, come in here.
You're gonna dig this.
[upbeat music on TV]
Oh, there I am. I'm on,
I'm on.. This is so exciting.
I'm Martha Quinn and
welcome to "Out of the Blue"
where we feature new artists
you've never heard of
and may never hear of again.
You might hear of me again,
right?
Well, you know,
it's not up to me.
It's up to you out there.
And this nervous gentleman
sitting next to me
is Jesse Katsopolis from
the hot new bay area band
Jesse & The Rippers.
Hey, I'm Jesse, hi.
Hi, why don't you use that,
right there, that camera?
I thought you'd wanna cut
to the close-up camera
'cause I'm having a good
hair day and everything.
'Sorry, it's your show.'
I just wanna say thanks
for having me on the show
Martha, Martha Quinn.
And uh, you know,
I just wanna say out there
that it's been
a very hard struggle
you know, a lot of..
Lot of sleepless nights
rejection, you know,
actually cold sweats.
Stomach cramps, gas, a bit of,
a lot of gas, actually.
Okay, that's fascinating.
Why don't we get to the video.
It is called "Forever"--
Okay, I just wanted
to say thanks real fast.
Thank you out there to Danny,
Joey, Stephanie and D.J.
- Oh, that's very sweet, so--
- I'm not done yet.
Michelle, my favorite little
munchkin. Hey, Michelle.
My beautiful wife, Rebecca,
I love you very much.
My two twins, Nicky and Alex,
adorable kids, really.
Do you hear that, boys?
You're famous.
- This one's Nicky.
- Okay, we're out of time now.
- What we'll do is just bring--
- Wa-wa-wait.
- Are you gonna show my video?
- Okay, just kidding.
You're not gonna have
a gas attack now, are you?
No.
Okay, we're gonna get to it.
This is Jesse & The Rippers.
Their brand new video
called "Forever"
which is a beach boys song,
isn't it?
Yeah, it's a beach boys song.
I know the beach boys.
- They sang on it, we're--
- Great. Here we go.
We're gonna roll it,
this is Jesse & The Rippers
and it is called "Forever."
"Forever."
[instrumental music]
[upbeat music]
♪ If every word I said ♪
♪ Could make you laugh ♪
♪ I'd talk forever ♪
♪ Together my love ♪
♪ I ask the sky what we had ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ It shone forever ♪
♪ Together my love ♪
♪ My my my.. ♪
♪ My my my ♪
♪ If the song I sing to you ♪
♪ Could fill your heart
with joy ♪
♪ I'd sing forever ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Together my love ♪
♪ my my my.. ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ I've been so happy
loving you ♪
[guitar solo]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Together my love ♪
♪ Let the love I have for you ♪
♪ Live in your heart ♪
♪ And beat forever ♪
♪ Together my love ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ I've been so happy
loving you ♪
♪ Woah ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ If every word I said ♪
♪ Could make you laugh ♪
♪ I'd talk forever ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Na na na ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ I've been so happy
loving you ♪♪
(Martha on TV)
'I'm Martha Quinn,
welcome to Out of the Blue'
'where we feature new artists
you've never heard of.'
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
That was the greatest
two and a half minutes
I've ever experienced
in my life.
- Hey.
- I mean, musically.
So, Jess, how does it feel
to be a big rock star?
Oh, I'm not a big rock star,
I mean, I just have one single.
I mean, who knows if people
are gonna buy it or not.
I don't wanna get you
over excited.
But, I went to the music store
to buy a copy
and they were completely
sold-out.
- Oh!
- Alright.
Well, I may have had, you know,
just a tiny bit to do with that.
I bought every copy they had.
- One for you.
- Thank you.
One for you.
- One for you.
- Thank you.
Comet, my man.
[instrumental music]
Joey, my man.
Here, Steph.
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪